insidestl.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy

_**PRIVACY POLICY**_

insideSTL Enterprises, LLC and its affiliates respect your privacy and believe the best way to serve you on the internet is with honesty, accountability and adherence to legal standards.  We are sensitive to the issue of privacy and have structured our online activities to maximize your control over the disclosure of your own personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy supplements our general Terms of Use, which we also urge you to read.  By using our Web site (the “Site”), you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and by the Terms of Use.  We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to the Site, and your continued use of the Site indicates your agreement to the revised terms.  Accordingly, we urge you to frequently review this Privacy Policy, and, if you do not agree to the terms of this or any revised policy, please exit the Site immediately.

PRIVACY OF CHILDREN  
Privacy of Children

insideSTL Enterprises, LLC encourages parents and guardians to be aware of and participate in their children's online activities. We strictly adhere to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly register or otherwise collect personally identifiable information from any child under the age of 13 without the prior verifiable consent of that person’s parent or guardian.

What Information is Collected.

insideSTL Enterprises, LLC may collect two types of information about you: personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address) and aggregate information that is anonymous (such as your IP address - a number used to identify your computer when you are on the Internet - or the type of browser you are using).

Personally Identifiable Information: You may be required to register or otherwise voluntarily provide personally identifiable information to have access to some features of the Site. You always may choose not to provide the personally identifiable information, but this may lead to decreased functionality of the Site for you and our inability to provide you with certain products or services. We also may request you to voluntarily provide personally identifiable information that is not required to access features of our site. This information enables insideSTL Enterprises, LLC to make general improvements to the Site and better serve your specific interests.

Aggregate Information: insideSTL Enterprises, LLC may transparently collect aggregate information through the use of cookies or by other means. We use this information to assess general usage patterns, administer and make improvements to the Site and collect demographic information useful in some way to insideSTL Enterprises, LLC and our business partners. We hope that by using Aggregate Information, we can update the Site to make it more useful to you and other users. We, and our business partners, reserve the right to use, maintain, update, disclose and/or sell Aggregate Information.

What We Will and Will Not Do with the Information You Provide

insideSTL Enterprises, LLC uses information generally to compile statistical data, keep in contact with users and provide them with a better interactive experience.

We may use your information specifically for the following purposes: to provide easy access every time you return to the site without requiring re-entry of registration information; to keep you informed about products and services in which you may have interest; to complete business transactions; to contact you as part of a promotion; to allow you to make a posting on the Site; to administer individual accounts; to provide customer support; to meet legal requirements; to provide Internet security; and/or to analyze the collected information. Also, in the event that we are involved in a sale of a substantial portion of our business assets, customer information may be among the transferred assets.

insideSTL Enterprises, LLC works closely with our business partners and certain other third parties who may perform functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, providing promotional materials to our users, sending e-mail, managing data, processing credit card payments or providing customer service. They have access to your personally identifiable information only to the extent necessary to perform their functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Further, these business partners and other third parties may from time to time wish to extend special offers to you on their own behalf. We may use your personally identifiable information to assist our business partners in offering you these products, services and information and may act as an intermediary (for instance, sending you e-mail on their behalf).

Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any third parties unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally compelled to do so. In addition, we will not contact you without your permission except as specified above or in connection with the registration process. On the Site, you will be given the opportunity to opt out of receiving e-mails or other information from insideSTL Enterprises, LLC. If you have questions about how your personally identifiable information is used, please contact us.

Third-Party Advertising: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Cookies

When you visit the Site, we or a third-party advertiser may store or recognize some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file that can help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor our site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the Site may be severely limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the Site's best features.
